Atlantic States Legal Foundation; Records apap311
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Projects, 1967-2009; Undated; 1; 118.92 cubic ft.
  - Northeast, 1970-2009; Undated; 1.2
    - New York - Pan American Tanning Corp. Court Documents, Joint Appendix, 1992 (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - New York - Pan American Tanning Corp. Permit, 1989-1990 (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - New York - Penn Quality Meats Cooperative Correspondence, Intent to Sue Standing, and Notes, 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - New York - Penntech Papers All Seasons Study of Total Suspended Solids, 1987-1988 (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - New York - Penntech Papers Discharge Sampling, Laboratory and Reporting Procedures Manual, Undated (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - New York - Penntech Papers-"Emergency and Backup Power Needs of the Waste Treatment Facilities", Undated (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - New York - Penntech Papers-"The Need of Spare Parts/Chemicals/Supplies for Water Pollution Control Equipment", Undated (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - New York - Penntech Papers Wastewater Treatment System Operations and Procedures Manual, Undated (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - New York - Penntech Papers Wastewater Treatment Upgrade Delaware - Conceptual Design Report, April, 1987 (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - New York - Perfection Plating Inc. Permit, 1976 (Box 25 (1-Projects), Folder 38)
    - New York - Pfauder-U.S. Inc. Correspondence, Notes, Permit, and Discharge Reports, 1982; 1987-1990; 1992 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Phillips ECG, Inc. Correspondence and Map, 1982-1987; Undated (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Phillips ECG, Inc. Court Documents, 1982-1983; 1986-1988 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Phillips ECG, Inc. Notes, 1982; 1985-1986; Undated (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Phillips ECG, Inc. Permits and DMR, 1978; 1982-1985 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Pico Products Inc. Correspondence, Notes, and Newsclipping, 1984; 1989-1990; Undated (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Pico Products Inc. Memo to ASLF from Pico Products, 1989 November 15 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Pico Products Inc. Permit and DMR, 1983; 1988-1989 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Plattsburg POTW Notes, 1990 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - PM Refining Inc. Correspondence and Notes, 1990-1992 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - PM Refining Inc. Correspondence and Notes, 1993 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - PM Refining Inc. Court Documents, 1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - PM Refining Inc. Court Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - PM Refining Inc. Permit, Chemical Survey, and EPA Forms, 1987; 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Port Authority Airport Correspondence, Intent to Sue, and Court Documents, 1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Port Authority, Goethals' Bridge-Intent to Sue, 1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Port Authority, JFK Airport, SPDES-Permit and Standing Questionnaire, 1988; 1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Port Authority, LaGuardia Airport-Intent to Sue, 1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Port Authority, Outerbridge Crossing Toll Plaza-Intent to Sue, 1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Poughkeepsie, City of, Correspondence, 1988-1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - New York - Primary Plastics Inc. Correspondence, Notes, and Discharge, 1987; 1990 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Pringer Services, Inc. Court Documents and Correspondence, 1983 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Production Products Co. Correspondence, Notes, EPA Forms, Discharge Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Production Products Co. Court Documents, 1989 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - R.E. Dietz Co. Correspondence, Court Documents, and Notes, 1989-1990 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - R.E. Dietz Co. Correspondence, EPA Forms, and Hazardous Waste Reports, 1987-1988 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - New York - Ramp Industries Inc. Correspondence, Notes, and Hazardous Waste Manifest, 1990; 1992 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Revere Copper Products, Inc. Correspondence and DMR, 1990-1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co.-Bioconcentration of PCBs in Fathead Minnows, 1994 January (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co.-Citizen's Guide to Lawrence River-Point Source of Toxic Chemicals, 1988 July 14 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co.-Citizen's Guide to Lawrence River-Point Source of Toxic Chemicals, 1988 August 15 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Consent Decree, 1987-1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Consent Decree, 1992 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 33-34)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Consent Order, 1993 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence, 1998 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence, 2001 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence and Notes, 1987 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 38)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence, 1988 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 39)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence and Notes, 1989 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 40)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence, 1990 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 41)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence and Notes, 1991 (Box 26 (1-Projects), Folder 42)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence and Notes, 1992 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence and Notes, 1993 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Correspondence and Notes, Undated (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Court Documents, 1988 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Court Documents, 1989 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Court Documents, 1990 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 6-7)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Court Documents, 1992 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Construction of the Landfill Drainage Water Treatment System, 1992 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co.-DEC Correspondence, 1978; 1983-1989 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Discharges of PCBs-Exceedence of Interim Effluent Limits, 1992 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. DMR, 1988 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Draft Final Feasibility Study Report, St. Lawrence Reduction Plant, 1991 February 08 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 13-16)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Drawings, 1994 (Flat-file 3)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Engineering Report for the 001 Sediment Basin, 1994 June (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. EPA Forms and Chemical Inventory, 1988 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Final Remedial Investigation-Revised Report, 1990 July 02 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Hygiene Protocols for PCBs, 1992 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Interim Remediation Activities Report, 1989 January 19 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Interim Remediation Completion-Revised Plan, 1989 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Interim Remediation Plan, 1988 October 19 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co., James Bay Update #22, 1993 February 15 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Maps, 1990 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1991 (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 February (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 March (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 April (Box 27 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 May (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 1-2)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 June (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 3-4)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 July (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 5-6)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 August (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 September (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 October (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 November (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1992 December (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 February (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 March (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 April (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 June (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 July (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 August (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 September (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 October (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 November (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 December (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1993 (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1994 January-1994 March (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1994 April (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1994 May (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1994 June (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1994 July-1994 September (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1994 December (Box 28 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1995 January-1995 March (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1995 April-1995 June (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1995 July-1995 September (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1995 October-1995 December (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1996 January-1996 March (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1996 April-1996 June (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 6-7)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1996 July-1996 September (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1996 October-1996 December (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1997 January-1997 March (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1997 April-1997 June (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1997 July-1997 September (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1997 October-1997 December (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1998 January-1998 April (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1998 June-1998 August (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1998 September-1998 October (Box 29 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1998 November-1998 December (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1999 January-1999 February (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1999 March-1999 April (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1999 May-1999 June (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1999 July (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1999 September-1999 October (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 1999 November-1999 December (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2000 January-2000 February (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2000 March-2000 May (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2000 June-2000 August (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2000 September-2000 December (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2001 January-2001 March (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2001 April (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2001 May (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2001 June (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2001 July-2001 September (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2001 October-2001 December (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2002 January-2002 February (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2002 March-2002 April (Box 30 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2002 May-2002 June (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2002 July-2002 August (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2002 September-2002 October (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2002 November-2002 December (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2003 January-2003 March (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2003 April-2003 June (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2003 July-2003 September (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2003 October-2003 December (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2004 January-2004 February (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Monthly Wastewater Monitoring, 2004 March-2004 April (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. PCB Analysis, 1986-1989 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 11-12)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. PCB Sampling Program, Work Plan, 1988 April (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. PCB Site Discharge List and Notes, 1991 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. PCB Soil Sampling Program, 1988 October 12 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. PCB Source Assessment Phase 4A Report, 1992 June 10 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. PCB Source Assessment Phase 4A Work Plan, 1990 February (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. PCB Source Assessment Revised Plan, 1989 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. PCB Source Identification Assessment, 1988 July 29 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. PCB Source Identification Assessment, 1989 February 20 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co.-PCDF/PCDD Sampling Report, 1989 January 10 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Permit, 1980-1981; 1985 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Permit, 1998; 2001; 2003 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Permit, 2004 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Permit Modification Stipulation, 1992 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Permits, 1991 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Photograph Description Notes, 1991 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Photographs, Roll 1, ca. 1991 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Photographs, Roll 2, ca. 1991 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Preliminary Conceptual Remediation-Plan PCB Contamination, 1988 July 29 (Box 31 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co., Proposed 001 Sedimentation Basin-Meeting Minutes, 1993 July 01 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Protocol for Monitoring Biocencentration of PCBs in Fathead Minnows Exposed, 1992 July 10 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Remediation of the 008 Outfall/West Ditch System and Remediation of the 007 Outfall, 1992 November (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Remediation of the 008 Outfall/West Ditch System Project Completion Report, 1992 November (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Remediation of the 008 Outfall/West Ditch System Work and Plan Schedule, 1992 August (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co.-St. Lawrence River Joint Monitoring Workshop, 1992 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co.-St. Lawrence River Sediment Sampling-Program Final Report, 1988 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co.-St. Regis Mohawk Tribe, 1989; 1988-1989; 1992 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Sampling, 1989-1990 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Standard Operating Procedure for Measuring the Bioconcentration of PCBs in Fathead Minnows, 1992 October (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Site Drainage Map, 1991 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Solid Waste Management-ACT Report, 1986 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Status Report, Contingency Follow-Up Investigation and Remediation for the 001 Discharge System, 1993 February (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Superfund Proposed Plan, 1993; Undated (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Transmittal of Joint Application for Permit, 1991-1992 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Treatment Optimization Study Program Workplan, 1992 February (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Unidentified Photographs, Undated (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Violation Summary, 1997 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. vs. AETNA, Casualty & Surety Co., 1996-1997 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Work Plan for Method 608-Method Detection Limit Study, 1990 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Work Plan for Method 608-Sampling and Analysis, 1992 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. Work Plan for Modification of the 006 Outfall, 1992 March (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. 001 Discharge System Cleanup Activities-Final Project Report, 1992 June (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. 001 Discharge System Contingency Follow-Up-Investigative/Remedial Work Plan, 1990 April (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. 001 Outfall Sediment Remedial System Conceptual Drawings, 1994 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. 001 Outfall System Catch Basin Cleanout-Final Project Report, 1992 August (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. 002 Outfall Diversion Plan, 1989 April 14 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. 003 and 004 Outfalls Optimization-Interim Report, 1993 November (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. 003 and 004 Outfalls Treatment and Optimization Study Report, 1994 November (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. 006 Outfall Modification Project Completion Report, 1992 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - New York - Reynolds Metals Co. 008 Work Plan and Schedule for the Investigation and Remediation, 1992 June (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - New York - Richard Rathbun Dairy Farm Correspondence, 1996-2000 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - New York - Richard Rathbun-Newsclipping and Research Material, 1992; 1995-1997 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - New York - Rick Hamelin-Correspondence, 1990; 1994; 1996 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - New York - Rick Hamelin-Correspondence, 1999 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - New York - Rick Hamelin-Correspondence, 2000 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - New York - Rick Hamelin-Correspondence, 2001; 2003 (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - New York - Rick Hamelin-Correspondence and Notes, Undated (Box 32 (1-Projects), Folder 38)